Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The changing character of American industry, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
    Notes: Papers delivered at the conference on the changing character of American industry, January 16, 1958. 2 copies
  - Item 5: This is the AFL-CIO: a democratic organization of 15 million Americans dedicated to building a stronger America., 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: America's responsibility for the preservation of human freedom, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Religion and labor, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: American and Soviet economy: contrast and comparison, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Legal case against 14-B, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Get America back to work: an AFL-CIO program for action., 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Research serves labor, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The Relationship of price to economic stability and growth: commentaries (reprinted from Joint Committee Print, Oct. 31, 1958), Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Must America continue to make progress through tragedy?, 1958; Publication (Box 441, Folder 1)
- George Meany, Publication (Box 441, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor looks at automation, 1956; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Research Dept.
  - Item 2: ABC's of trade unionism, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The World's refugees: a challenge to America, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Analysis of the "Labor management reporting and disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: How to apply - 1960 AFL-CIO College Merit, Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Freedom forever labor rejects Communism, Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Justice for the jobless, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Prequntas y respuestas, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Policy resolution on housing, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Going first class., 1956; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Your rights under fair employment practice laws, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
    Notes: Revised edition
  - Item 12: How to organize a credit union, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Questions and answers on American labor and world affairs, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Farmers and workers., 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Unemployment compensation: too little, too late, for too few, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
    Author: A. J. Hayes
  - Item 16: Better minimum wage for more American workers: costs no more than 1 [cent] per $1 of payroll, Publication (Box 441, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Text of AFL-CIO labor bill statement, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Survey of union financial practices, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: TheAmerican Federationist -- UNESCO: A growing force for good, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
    Author: Frank Fernbach
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO statement on proposal to increase interest rates on long term bonds, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Build the necessary classrooms, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Care News - Special AFL-CIO Edition, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Better schools for a better America, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Our finest weapon, education, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
    Notes: Reprinted from April and May, 1959. Second copy
  - Item 9: How to reach the union member, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: AFL-CIO safety program, 1959; Publication (Box 441, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Your rights under fair employment practice laws, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
    Notes: Revised edtion. Second copy
  - Item 2: Union political activity spans 230 years of U.S. history., 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Civil rights in the AFL-CIO, 1961; Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Why more trade?, 1961; Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Medical care for the aged, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Lookout below, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: When great men agree, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Why labor fights for civil rights, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: What is the union, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The basic principles of foreign aid, Publication (Box 441, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Safety in numbers, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The hidden cost of not belonging, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Can you afford to be 65?, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Automation, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The New York Times, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
    Notes: May 8, 1960 - Section 102 copies
  - Item 6: Railroad mergers, 1961; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Civil rights in the AFL-CIO, 1961; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining Report, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (91960)
  - Item 9: correspondence -- Dear Friend: In response to your request for information on compulsory health insurance, we are sending you the enclosed materials which I hope will be helpful, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Aging basic needs and programs, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Statement of before the Senate Finance Committee in support of adding health benefits through social security to H.R. 12580, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: The impact of automation - a challenge to America, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Captains in revolt, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
    Author: H.W. Benson
  - Item 14: Unemployment insurance under state laws, Jan. 1, 1960, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: article-How its done in Sweden, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
    Author: Lisbeth Bamberger
  - Item 16: National Health Insurance Bibliography, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Britains Natation Health Service - Misleading charges about the National Health Service are being circulated in the United States, 1961; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: President Meany speaks at the United Nations, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Labor and world peace, Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: The Crisis in American Medicine: a special supplement of Harper's, 1960; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: A new look at health insurance, 1955; Publication (Box 441, Folder 6)
    Author: Al Hayes
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Consumer, beware!, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Fair taxes for good schools, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Labor, champion of public education, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Edward P. Morgan and the news, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: When you write your Congressman, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Get crooks-not unions!, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Discrimination costs too much, Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Negro fight against segregation finds inspiration in labor's past, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from: AFL-CIO News
  - Item 9: 20 ideas for steward meetings, Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Why labor fights for civil rights, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Policy resolution on organizing the unorganized, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Federal aid to education: a step toward real partnership, 1961; Publication (Box 442, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Workmen's Compensation under state laws.., 1962; Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Get America back to work, 1962; Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: A strong America - for peace and freedom, Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Equal opportunity for higher education, Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: This is the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Labor looks at our schools, Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Facts: old age health insurance is everybody's business, Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Labor looks at education, 1962; Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Why unions?, 1962; Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
    Notes: Revised edition. 2 copies
  - Item 10: Labor looks at education, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: America's health needs: the government's role, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Trade Adjustment: the new realism, 1962; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Notes: Flyer. This article was prepared in May 1962. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Look out below, Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The New York Times, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Notes: Nov. 17, 1963 - Section 11
  - Item 5: The new breed of demagogue, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Author: David L. Perlman
  - Item 6: The trade union and you, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining: its political implications, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Meany to industry - aid Latin progress, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Impact of 'right-to-work' laws, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Author: Milton J. Nadworny
  - Item 10: Labor and civil liberties, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Tax cut needed to make more jobs..., 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Correspondence - Dear Friend, Since 1958 the AFL-CIO has maintained a labor research internship program through which an outstanding graduate student has been able to spend a year working in a professional capacity in our Research Dept., 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Unemployment Insurance under state laws, July 1, 1963, Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Adjusting to automation, 1969; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Author: Rudolph A. Oswald
  - Item 15: The total challenge of automation, 1963; Publication (Box 442, Folder 3)
    Notes: Address -- before the Fifth Constitutional Convention, AFL-CIO, Americana Hotel, New York City -- November 19, 1963. 2 copies
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Why labor endorses Johnson and Humphrey, Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Civil rights: facts vs. fiction, Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Helping to write your nation's laws, Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Filibuster: a story of Democracy inaction, Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Group health - a better way to good health care, Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Civil rights: statement adopted by AFL-CIO Exec. Council.., Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The truth about "right to work" laws: facts vs. propaganda, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
    Notes: Revised edtion.
  - Item 8: Labor fights the enemies of democracy, 1964; Publication (Box 442, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Advance --- article - The fight to protect your vote, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO takes action on the Kingsport Press, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1965 Roll call, Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO in Buffalo, Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Democracy inaction!, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Higher education for all who want to learn, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
    Author: Harry Boyer
    Notes: A plan for the development of our greatest resource, our young people: a statement of labor's position presented by the Pennsylvania AFL-CIO by its president, Harry Boyer, at a public hearing conducted by the State Council of Higher Education, February 2
  - Item 7: Collective bargaining, democracy on the job, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: How false work laws keep South's pay low, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Dirksen's real beef, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: How your Senators and Representatives voted 1963-1964 (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Labor's goal to end poverty in our time, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The vital links, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Opening day program 6th Constitutional Convention -- AFL-CIO, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Religious Leaders back free collective bargaining; What do you tell them about 14 (b), 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Labor's role in the war on poverty, 1967; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: The truth about "right to work" laws: facts vs. propaganda, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
    Notes: Revised edition. Second copy
  - Item 17: Policy resolutions on international affairs, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
    Notes: Adopted December, 1965 by the Sixth Constitutional Convention American Federation of Labor, Congress of Industrial Organizations.
  - Item 18: 'Right to work' laws lower labor standards, 1965; Publication (Box 442, Folder 5)
    Author: AFL- CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Research Dept.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Sample speeches for labor groups -- business groups --, Publication (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Information on Radio advertising, Publication (Box 442, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Statements from Religious leaders about the 'right-to-work' laws, Publication (Box 442, Folder 6)